A Guide to the Weaver-Brady Papers
University of Virginia Library
Haxale (P.) & Co., Richmond, Va. (L. R. Haxale agent) (1829 Jan. 28, ALS, to W. W., re: short order) (1829 Mar. 18, ALS, to W. W., re: examination of piece of rolled iron) (1829 May 29, ALS, to W. W., re: an iron order) (1829 June 30, ALS, to W. W., re: order of state iron) (1830 July 12, ALS, to W. W., re: order of nails and iron by W. Cummings)
[Hench] Nancy (In non correspondence -receipt)
Heck, D. (1859 Feb. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: delivery of more iron)
Hobbs, Nathaniel R. (In non correspondence)
Hoffman, John (In non correspondence -receipt)
Hollins (M.) & Co., Lynchburg, Va. (1862 Jan. 9, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order)
Holmes, Simon (In non correspondence)
Hough, John A. (In non correspondence)
Hughes, William W. (1829 Nov. 2, ALS, Wm. A [Daturk] to Hughes, re: Hughes debt to Daturk)
Hull, Philip (In non correspondence -receipts)
Hutcheson, David (ln non correspondence -legal)
[Hyal], C. (In non correspondence -receipts and bills)
Irby & Saunders, Lynchburg, Va. (1859 Jan. 29, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1859 Dec. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (In non correspondence)
Jennings and Jones, Cartersville, Va. (1829 Feb. 26, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1829 Mar. 27, ALS, to W. W., re: delay of iron order)
Johnson, George W. (1861 July 5, ALS, to W. W., re: renewal of promissory note)
Johnson, Younger, & Otey, Richmond, Va. (1859 Mar. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: suggestion to W. W. that he sell his bar iron in Richmond) (1859 Mar. 22, ALS, to W. W., re: shipment of sugar and coffee) (1859 Apr. 5, ALS, to W. W., re: bill for goods delivered by boat) (1859 Apr. 28, ALS, to W. W., re: disputed bill) (1859 May 12, ALS, to W. W., re: buckets) (1859 June 12, ALS, to W. W., re: handbill of Rice and Brenstone) (1859 June 15, ALS, to W. W., re: order of rice) (1859 June 23, ALS, to W. W., re: sugar) (1859 July 18, ALS, to W. W., re: payment for goods bought) (1859 July 26, ALS, to W. W., re: tea) (1859 Aug. 1, ALS, to W. W., re: cost of bacon) (1859 Aug. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: sale of meat) (1859 Aug. 13, ALS, to W. W., re: bill for bacon) (1859 Aug. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: receipt of goods) (1859 Sept. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: shipment of requested articles) (1859 Oct. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: new bill) (1859 Oct. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: general business relations) (1859 Oct. 31, ALS, to W. W., re: business) (1859 Nov. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: general business) (1861 Mar. 13, ALS, to W. W., re: nails) (1861 Mar. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: note due) (1861 May 27, ALS, to W. W., re: payment of note)
Johnston, Chapman (In non correspondence -receipt)
Jones, C. C. [Treasurer of Craige Co.] (1891 Mar. 12, ALS, to Jas. M. Ambler, re: David Hoffman's tax bills) (1891, ALS, to Randolph Barton and Geo. A. VanLingen, re: bill)
Jones, Warner (1841 May 14, ALS, to Dorman and Davidson, re: law suit by Mrs. Ellen Maybury)
Jones and Miller, Lynchburg, Va. (1862 Sept. 11, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1862 Nov. 12, ALS, to W. W., re: purchased iron which never arrived)
Jordan (1853 July 6, ALS, to son Edwin, re: land sale)
Jordan, Benjamin J. (In non correspondence -legal)
Jordan, Edwin (1853 July 6, ALS, Jordan to son Edwin, re: land sale) (1853 July 9, ALS, to father, re: purchase of some property) (In non correspondence -legal)
Jordan, Ira F. (In non correspondence -legal)
Jordan, John (1851 Dec. 15, ALS, W. W. to Jordan, re: disputed land boundary) (1853 Feb. 15, ALS, Peter A. Salling to W. W. and Jordan, re: disposition of Jn. Poague) (In non correspondence -legal)
Jordan, W. H. (1862 Apr. 2, ALS, to W. W., re: iron affairs)
Jordan, William (1862 May 30, ALS, to W. W., re: request that W. Brady meet Jordan and F. T. Glasgow in Lexington) (In non correspondence)
Jordan and Irvine (1831 Feb. 10, ALS, to W. W., re: filling order for pig metal) (1831 July 14, ALS, to W. W., re: tubs) (In non correspondence -bills and receipts)
Jordan, Davis & Co.;; Bath Iron Works; [Samuel F. Jordan and; William W. Davis] (1831 Feb. 2, ALS, to W. W., re: account) (1831 May 14, ALS, to A. W. Davis, re: transport of additional metal) (1831 May 15, ALS, to A. W. Davis, re: metal order) (1831 June 17, ALS, to A. W. Davis, re: coffee) (1831 June 28, ALS, to A. W. Davis, re: wind mill) (1831 June 29, ALS, to A. W. Davis, re: load of corn) (1831 July 15, ALS, to A. W. Davis, re: coal) (1831 Aug. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: linen and flax) (1831 Sept. 9, ALS, to W. W., re: forge plates) (1831 Nov. 30, ALS, to W. W., re: shelling machine castings) (1831 Dec. 22, ALS, to W. W., re: pair of shoes) (1840 Aug. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: trespassing on the property of Jordan nd Davis) (1849 May 2, ALS, to C.D. Moore, re: the case of Weaver v. Jordan & Davis) (1862 Feb. 12, ALS, to Brady, re: order of railroad spikes) (In non correspondence -bills and receipts)
Kayser, William B. (1877 Dec., ALS, to Brady, re: recommendation for Samuel Beard)
Kayton, John (In non correspondence -receipt)
Kent, Paine & Co., Richmond, Va. (1859 Jan. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: note due for $417.66) (1859 Feb. 24, ALS, to W. W., re: business with Lee, Rocke & Co.) (1859 May 2, ALS, to W. W., re: sample of woolen goods) (1859 May 11, ALS, to W. W., re: goods arrived by boat) (1859 May 17, ALS, to W. W., re: bale of sheetings) (1859 Aug. 27, ALS, to W. W., re: manganese) (1859 Dec. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: payment of bill) (1861 Jan. 21, ALS, to W. W., re: settlement of debt) (1861 Mar. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: sale of "brown" cotton) (1861 May 3, ALS, to W. W., re: goods ordered) (1861 June 12, ALS, to W. W., re: clothes) (1862 Dec. 13, ALS, to W. W., re: sheetings) (In non correspondence -bills and receipts)
Kop and Preston (In non correspondence)
Kyle, (Daniel and; Robert), Lynchburg, Va. (1829 Apr. 10, ALS, to W. W., re: delivery of iron by Bootman)
Ladyaed, Elizabeth (1857 Nov. 9, ALS, to uncle W. W., re: inquiry of farm near Lexington)
Lair, J. T. (1851 Dec. 19, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: purchase of Hite farms)
Laird & Bros., Kerr's Creek (1859 Sept. 14, ALS, to W. W., re: sides of meat)
Landers, Irby (In non correspondence --order, 1859)
Lankford, William J. (1851 July 4, ALS, to George Bagby, re: the dissolution of partnership of Martin and Better)
Layton, William (In non correspondence --receipts)
Leach, James H. (1861 Mar. 11, ALS, to W. W., re: denial of charge of cutting timber on W. W.'s land; general affairs in the iron business)
Lee, Johnson & Co. (In non correspondence --receipt)
Lee, Rocke & Co., Lynchburg, Va. (1859 Jan. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: note for $2000) (1859 Jan. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: collection of notes) (1859 Jan. 22, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1859 Feb. 1, ALS, to W. W., re: order of goods on "2 Belle") (1859 Feb. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: delivery of iron) (1859 Feb. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: delivery of leather, etc.) (1859 Feb. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: purchase of iron goods) (1859 Mar. 2, ALS, to W. W., re: inquiry as to why order was not received) (1859 Mar. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: notice of articles sent) (1859 Mar. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1859 Mar. 12, ALS, to W. W., re: order for two tons of iron) (1859 Mar. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: notice of ordered iron not delivered) (1859 Mar. 29, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1859 Mar. 31, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1859 Apr. 9, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's acct. with Lee, Rocke & Co.) (1859 Apr. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: note for $1000 for 60 days) (1859 May 7, ALS, to W. W., re: request to send orders yet unfulfilled) (1859 May 17, ALS, to W. W., re: cotton goods) (1859 May 24, ALS, to W. W., re: request for pig iron) (1859 May 24, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's bill) (1859 May 26, ALS, to W. W., re: payment of note for $1000) (1859 June 7, ALS, to W. W., re: order for iron) (1859 June 9, ALS, to W. W., re: order for iron) (1859 July 14, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1859 July 18, ALS, to W. W., re: goods ordered; note of J. C. Moore) (1859 July 24, ALS, to W. W., re: sale of oats) (1859 July 30, ALS, to W. W., re: iron sales) (1859 Aug. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: bacon and ham) (1859 Aug. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: order for two tons of iron) (1859 Aug. 29, ALS, to W. W., re: itemized order of iron) (1859 Sept. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1859 Sept. 6, ALS, to W. W., re: correction of an error) (1859 Sept. 10, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1859 Sept. 17, ALS, to W. W., re: correction of interest error; iron order) (1859 Sept. 29, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1859 Oct. 11, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1859 Oct. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: solvency of James Bryot Co.) (1859 Oct. 30, ALS, to W. W., re: order of scollop iron) (1859 Nov. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: articles) (1859 Nov. 7, ALS, to W. W., re: delivery of certain articles) (1859 Nov. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: delivery of articles) (1859 Dec. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: hides) (In non correspondence)
Lee, Rocke & Taylor, Lynchburg, Va. (1861 Jan. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: note for $1176.75) (1861 Feb. 2, ALS, to W. W., re: metal delivery) (1861 Feb. 13, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order; Republican party and breaking the union) (1861 Feb. 21, ALS, to W. W., re: grocery deliveries and general news) (1861 Mar. 1, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1861 Mar. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1861 Mar. 12, ALS, to W. W., re: orders for supplies) (1861 Mar. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1861 Mar. 27, ALS, to W. W., re: unpaid bill) (1861 Apr. 5, ALS, to W. W., re: bill for tar) (1861 Apr. 12, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1861 June 8, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's bill; war; restrictions) (1861 June ll, ALS, to W. W., re: bill) (1861 Dec. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: salt) (1861 Dec. 7, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1862 Jan. 27, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1862 Feb. 11, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1862 Feb. 17, ALS, to W. W., re: sale of railroad iron to Charles Scott) (1862 Feb. 27, ALS, to W. W., re: sale of railroad iron to Charles Scott) (1862 Mar. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1862 Apr. 24, ALS, to W. W., re: balance in account; other business) (1862 May 6, ALS, to W. W., re: W. W.'s acct.) (1862 May 12, ALS, to W. W., re: goods to various concerns) (1862 May 15, ALS, to W. W., re: sugar) (1862 May 22, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1862 May 24, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1862 Oct. 18, ALS, to W. W., re: iron shipment) (1862 Nov. 3, ALS, to W. W., re horse collars) (l862 Nov. 12, ALS, to W. W., re: bill for mule collars) (1862 Dec. 16, ALS, to W. W., re: business) (In non correspondence)
Leech, John S. (In non correspondence)
[Letcher], John (1849 Dec. 7, ALS, W. W. to Letcher, re: sawmill and sawing)
Letcher S. H. (In non correspondence -bills and receipts)
Lewis William C. (In non correspondence)
Lewis, Webb & Co. (In non correspondence -receipts)
Locher, Charlie H. (1859 Dec. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: corn and other supplies) (1861 May 10, ALS, to Brady, re: order of mackerel) (1862 June 28, ALS, to Brady, re: delay in L.'s arrival)
Lucas, William (In non correspondence)
Lusk, John A (1855 Jan. 17, ALS, to W. W, re: corn moved from Hart's Bottom)
Luster, John (1859 July 8, ALS, to W. W., re: better quality of shoe iron) (1862 Apr. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: general business affairs) (1862 May 27, ALS, to Brady, re: arrival of unidentified person)
Lyle, John H. (1859 Feb. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: meeting with Lyle) (1859 Nov. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: sale of sand) (1859 Dec. 6, ALS, to W. W., re: appraisal of sand land)
McCall, John (In non correspondence)
McCarty, William A. (1859 Apr. 6, ALS, to W. W., re: tire set) (1859 July 14, ALS, to W. W., re: inquiry into delivery of iron goods)
McClung and Surry (In non correspondence)
McClurg & T[urney], Philadelphia, Pa. (1829 Jan. 22, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's account)
McCorkle and Co. (1859 Jan. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: iron purchase) (1859 Jan. 21, ALS, to W. W., re: collection of some promissory notes) (1859 Mar. 15, ALS, to W. W., re: clearing of a balance) (In non correspondence -receipts)
McCorkle (G.M.) & McDaniel, Lynchburg, Va. (1835 Nov. 7, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's acct.) (In non correspondence -accts.)
McCorkle, Simpson & Jones, Lynchburg, Va. (1855 July 14, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: balance due by Bryan & Randolph to Davidson)
McCormick, Henry A. (1854 July 18, ALS, to W. W., re: planned trip) (1855 July 29, ALS, to W. W., re: embarcation for said trip) (1855 Dec. 29, ALS, to W. W., re: runaway negro) (1858 Aug. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: Lynchburg water works) (1858 Sept. 5, ALS, to W. W., re: six inch pipe) (1859 Jan. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: inquiry for a doctor) (1859 Feb. 14, ALS, to W. W., re: news of Dabney A. Trice) (1859 Feb. 21, ALS, to W. W., re: conclusion of affairs with Dabney A. Trice) (1859 Feb. 26, ALS, to W. W., re: wagon parts) (1859 Feb. 29, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: visit to W. W.) (1859 May 7, ALS, to W. W., re: iron trade) (1859 June 21, ALS, to W. W., re: health of various unidentified persons) (1859 July 14, ALS, to W. W., re: planting of oats) (1859 July 21, ALS, to W. W., re: growing season; sale of horses) (1859 Aug. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: personal news) (1859 Aug. 14, ALS, to W. W., re: purchase of a business by Dabney A. Trice (?) (1859 Nov. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: condition of the horses) (1862 Feb. 28, ALS, to W. W., re: clover seed)
McCutchan, William M. (1856 May 10, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: purchase of Weaver's land)
McCutchen, Samuel F. (In non correspondence)
McDaniel, Hart & Preston (In non correspondence)
McKinney & Co. (In non correspondence)
Mann, William A. (1862 May 12, ALS, to Brady, re: sale of old furnace property) (In non correspondence)
Martin, Frederick A. (In non correspondence)
Mathews, James William (1831 Mar. 2, ALS, to A. Davis, re: order of horse shoe iron and mold boards) (ln non correspondence)
Matthews and Harrison, Rockbridge Co. [agent -David Matthews] (1829 Mar. 2, ALS, to W. W., re: depositon of Edward Bryan et al.) (1829 Mar. 27, ALS, to W. W., re: acceptance of a deposition) (1829 July 25, ALS, to W. W., re: bond delivery)
[Maxwel], Henry D. (In non correspondence -legal)
Meem, John G. (1861 June 21, ALS, to W. W., re: inquiry into why iron has not been sent) (1861 June 22, ALS, to W. W., re: cloth)
Michie & Stuart; normal="Thomas G. Michie">[Thomas G. Michie and; A. H. H. Stuart] (In non correspondence)
Miller, James (In non correspondence)
Miller, S. S. (In non correspondence)
Miller, Samuel L (In non correspondence -receipts and bills)
Miller and Roberts, Lynchburg, Va. (1829 Jan. 21, ALS, to W. W., re: order for four tons of iron) (1829 Apr. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: undelivered iron shipment) (1833 Jan. 24, ALS, to W. W., re: boat load of iron) (In non correspondence)
Mitchell, Henry (In non correspondence -bills and receipts)
Moffit, William (1840 Sept.5, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: debt of Jordan and Davis)
Montgomery, R. (In non correspondence)
[Montyoung & Irvin] (1840 May, ALS to Dorman & Davidson, re: a suit against Montyoung by a Mr. Jordan)
Moon, Samuel O. (1829 Mar. 16, ALS, to W. W., re: inquiry into why iron ordered has not arrived)
M[oon], Lewis and Co. Scotsville, Va. (In non correspondence -bills and receipts)
Mooney, A. R. (1859 Apr. 6. ALS, to W. W. re: balance due on note)
Moore, [James] C. C. (1854 Nov. 10, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: four sacks of salt) (In non correspondence)
Moore, Samuel McDowell, 1796-1875 (1849 May 2, ALS, Samuel F. Jordan to Moore, re: the case of Weaver v. Jordan and Davis) (In non correspondence)
Moore & Davidson (In non correspondence)
Morgan, D. S. (1859 July l9, ALS, to W. W., re: salt)
Morris (A.), Richmond, Va. (1859 June 21, ALS, to W. W., re: Weaver's acct.)
Morris, [R.] (1829 Oct. 26, ALS, to W. W., re: price of Lindsy)
Murdoch Yville & Co. (?) (1829 June 30, ALS, to W. W., re: shipment of iron)
Murry, William (In non correspondence)
Myers, J. H. (1862 Feb. 19, ALS, to W. W., re: $5788.11 to the credit of W. W.)
Nash, James (In non correspondence)
Newkirke, White & Co. (In non correspondence)
Newman, Walter (1831 Sept. 26, ALS, to W. W., re: reply to a letter)
Newton, John (1855 Apr. 16, to J. D. Davidson, re: sale of land of E. Bujon)
Ninis, R. (?) (In non correspondence)
[Obenchay], George (1849 Nov. 27, ALS, to W. W., re: using Obenchey's books to obtain transactions with Sherrerd)
O'Brian, Lafayette (In non correspondence)
Old Dominion Iron & Nail Works Co., Richmond, Va. [William L. Triplett, Pres.] (1861 Nov. 29, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order) (1861 Dec. 5, ALS, to W. W., re: poor iron shipment)
Paine, Kent and Co. (In non correspondence -bills and receipts)
Patterson, R. T. (In non correspondence -receipt)
Paxton, D. E. (In non correspondence)
Paxton, E. F. (In non correspondence -legal)
Paxton, H. (In non correspondence -receipt)
Paxt[on], James G. (1862 Mar. 3, ALS, to W. W., re: wagon, shoes)
Paxton, James H. (1862 Feb. 28, ALS, to W. W., re: sale of mules)
Paxton, Thomas (In non correspondence)
Paxton, William (In non correspondence)
Potts, Nathaniel R. (1837 July 8, ALS, to W. W., re: deed of Weaver and wife to Jn. and Irwin France, legal matters)
Price, John H. (1862 Sept. 2, ALS, to W. W., re: iron order)
Randolph, James A. F. (1856 Feb. 2, ALS, to J. D. Davidson, re: acct. due Brian and Randolph) (In non correspondence)
Randolph & Buchanan, Cedar Grove Mills (In non correspondence)
Rex, Samuel V. (1859 Feb. 24, ALS, G. R. Fox to [Rex], re: getting money from W. W.) (1859 Feb. 25, ALS, to W. W., re: Mary Ann Hallman's estate)
Rex, William W. (1859 Jan. 8, ALS, to W.W.) (1858 Feb. 7, ALS, to W. W., re: report on the mine; send load of corn) (1859 Jan. 22, ALS, to Brady, re: load of corn) (1859 Jan. 26, ALS, to Brady, re: 2" bar) (1859 Jan. 28, ALS, to Brady, re: 2 iron bars) (1859 Feb. 15, ALS, to uncle W. W., re: iron goods) (1859 Feb. 19, ALS, to Brady, re: paucity of chop and oats) (1859 Feb. 19, ALS, to Brady, re: absence of feed) (1859 Feb. 22, ALS, to Brady, re: requests for chop, corn, and wings) (1859 Feb. 25, ALS, to Brady, re: salt for mules and a side of sole leather) (1859 Feb. 28, ALS, to Brady, re: supplies) (1859 Mar. 2, ALS, to W. W., re: coalering some wood) (1859 Mar 2, ALS, to Brady, re: plough shears) (1859 Mar. 4, ALS, to Brady, re: order for 1 x 2" tyre/tire?) (1859 Mar. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: answer to inquiry into the 20 pts. in the other bill) (1859 Mar. 10, ALS, to Brady, re: general business affairs) (1859 Mar. 11, ALS, to Brady, re: hiring an unidentified hand) (1859 Mar. 14, ALS, to Brady, re: continued work of Joseph Reid with his team) (1859 Mar. 16, ALS, to Brady, re: notice of shaft and flanges) (1859 Mar. 17, ALS, to Brady, re: inquiry into the readiness of seed oats) (1859 Apr. 4, ALS, to Brady, re: deliveries of chop) (1859 Apr. 7, ALS, to Brady, re: loan of trough) (1859 Apr. 8, ALS, to Brady, re: lack of powder) (1&59 Apr. 9, ALS, to Brady, re: load of straw) (1859 Apr. 23, ALS, to Brady, re: dry goods reserved for W. W.) (1859 May 10, ALS, to Brady, re: general news about the mill) (1859 May 19, ALS, to Brady, re: 2 shafts and 2 miter wheels) (1859 July 26, ALS, to Brady, re: bacon; complaints about bad meat) (1859 Aug. 18, ALS, to Brady, re: crow bars) (1859 Oct. 20, ALS, to [W. W.], re: request for 2 or 3 lbs of flour) (1859 Dec. 21, ALS, to Brady, re: general business affairs) (1859 Dec. 23, ALS, to Brady, re: distribution of clothing) (1859 Dec. 31, ALS, to Brady, re: request for 2 suits) (1859 Dec. 31, ALS, to Brady, re: mules) (1861 Jan. 8, ALS, to [W. W.], re: request for supplies) (1861 Jan. 11, ALS, to [W. W.], re: pattern) (l861 Jan. 22, ALS, to Brady, re: sending the furnace wheel segments and request for beef) (1861 Jan. 29, ALS, to Brady, re: business affairs) (1861 Feb. 15, ALS, to Brady, re: flour and iron order) (1861 Feb. 28, ALS, to Brady, re: order and request for iron and groceries) (1861 Mar. 7, ALS, to Brady, re: request for salt, seeds, etc. and other affairs) (1861 Mar. 15, ALS to Brady) (1861 Mar 25, ALS, to Brady, re: description of load of metal) (1861 Mar. 26, ALS, to Brady, re: affairs on ordered metal) (1861 Apr. 1, ALS, to Brady, re: potatoes) (1861 Apr. 6, ALS, to Brady, re: supplies at the mill) (1861 Apr. 13, ALS, to Brady, re: general business news) (1861 Apr. 16, ALS, to Brady, re: business news) (1861 May 3, ALS, to Brady, re: castings) (1861 May 9, ALS, to Brady, re: iron order, Jn.'s health) (1861 May 21, ALS, to Brady, re: request for bacon; forge business) (1861 May 24, ALS, to Brady, re: forge business) (1861 May 28, ALS, to Brady, re: forge affairs) (1861 June 1, ALS, to Brady, re: labor, girl to work) (1861 June 4, ALS, to Brady, re: state of readiness of iron products at the forge) (1861 June 7, ALS, to Brady, re: misc. orders) (1861 June 15, ALS, to Brady, re: leaking bellows) (1861 June 19, ALS, to Brady, re: poor repair of forge) (1861 June 26, ALS, to Brady, re: forge working again) (1861 June 29, ALS, to Brady, re: shipment of iron and general business workings around the foundary) (1861 July 4, ALS, to Brady, re: mill machinery) (1861 July 9, ALS, to Brady, re: iron affairs and sale of used goods) (1861 Aug. 9, ALS, to Brady, re: affairs at the forge) (1861 Sept. 13, ALS, to Brady, re: mistake in iron shipment) (1861 Sept. 17, ALS, to W. W., re: information leading to potential sale of iron) (1861 Sept. 21, ALS, to Brady, re: why metal shipment was delayed) (1861 Nov. 5, ALS, to Brady, re: request for corn feed and beef; general affairs at the forge) (1861 Nov. 23, ALS, to Brady, re: plank) (1861 Nov. 30, ALS, to Brady, re: statement of goods delivered) (1861 Dec. 3, ALS, to Brady, re: general business affairs) (1861 Dec. 10, ALS, to Brady, re: notice of metal prepared) (1861 Dec. 12, ALS, to Brady, re: general business news about the forge) (1861 Dec. 14, ALS, to Brady, re: general business affairs) (1862 Jan. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: metal which was not recorded) (1862 Jan. 7, ALS, to W. W., re: notice of potential iron sale) (1862 Jan. 8, ALS, to W. W., re: stolen metal) (1862 Jan. 9, ALS, to W. W., re: wagon load of coal bed) (1862 Jan. 10, 2 ALS, to W. W., re: boat arrival) (1862 Jan. 16, ALS, to Brady, re: general business) (1862 Jan. 21, ALS, to W. W., re: casting) (1862 Jan. 24, ALS, to W. W., re: inquiry into railroad and cylinder iron) (1862 Jan. 31, ALS, to Brady, re: report on affairs at the forge) (1862 Feb. 1, ALS, to Brady, re: shipment of iron) (1862 Feb. 4, ALS, to Brady, re: weather; state of metal) (1862 Feb. 7, ALS, to Brady, re: reason for delay in delivery) (1862 Feb. 13, ALS, to Brady, re: wood shaft; iron affairs) (1862 Feb. 20, ALS, to W. W., re: general business affairs) (1862 Mar. 4, ALS, to W. W., re: need for harnesses for the mules; other business affairs) (1862 Mar. 7, ALS, to W. W., re: general business affairs) (1862 Mar. l5, ALS, to Brady, re: general business affairs) (1862 Mar. 20, ALS, to Brady, re: metal shipment) (1862 Mar. 20, ALS, to Brady, re: iron news) (1862 Mar. 20, ALS, to Brady, re: iron news) (1862 Mar. 25, ALS, to Brady, re: iron news) (1862 May 3, ALS, to Brady, re: general affairs; request for tallow and flour) (1862 May 6, ALS, to Brady, re: plows) (1862 May 8, ALS, to Brady, re: scrap iron; supplies; iron affairs) (1862 May 10, ALS, to Brady, re: request for supplies; business affairs) (1862 May 14, ALS, to Brady, re: general business) (1862 May 16, ALS, to Brady, re: general business) (1862 May 24, ALS, to Brady, re: request for turpentine, etc.) (1862 May 29, ALS, to Brady, re: general business affairs) (1862 May 30, ALS, to Brady, re: affairs at the forge) (1862 June 3, ALS, to Brady, re: affairs at the forge) (1862 June 6, ALS, to Brady, re: affairs at the forge) (1862 June 12, ALS, to Brady, re: iron delivery affairs at the forge) (1862 June 14, ALS, to Brady, re: Louisa's property; corn bed; iron affairs) (1862 June 17, ALS, to Brady, re: general business affairs) (1862 June 19, ALS, to Brady, re: general affairs at the forge) (1862 June 25, ALS, to W. W., re: metal delivery; request for leather)